<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Louie&#39;s Site on Louie Yip 🐝</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Louie&#39;s Site on Louie Yip 🐝</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>everything burns</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/unhinged/everything_burns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/unhinged/everything_burns/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;the past few weeks have been an absolute shitshow.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.thenorthernecho.co.uk/news/25141807.newcastle-student-accommodation-evacuated-flat-fire/&#34;&gt;last sunday my house burned down.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;well that&amp;rsquo;s not true, first it&amp;rsquo;s a student accommodation, and secondly the fire only appeared on the top floor and thankfully didnt consume the whole building.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;but the damage was bad enough that we had to be relocated to temporary accommodation, where i was placed in some dingy hostel.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we weren&amp;rsquo;t even allowed back into our rooms to collect stuff until a few days after, so all i had with me since evacuating was my phone and wallet. thank god i brought those things otherwise i would have no money and no one to contact.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I got into Bees</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/01_beeginnings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/01_beeginnings/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have been thinking long and hard about the topic of my first ever post on my personal website, long enough to the point I&amp;rsquo;ve also contemplated when I should actually begin releasing content. Knowing that &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/World_Bee_Day&#34;&gt;World Bee Day&lt;/a&gt; is coming up (celebrated on the 20th of May every year), I figured that I would explain to you all how it all started: &lt;em&gt;how I got into bees.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It all began back when I was still studying for my bachelors degree at Imperial College London. I had joined a student-led society that did gardening as group activities, and indeed they had a quaint but decently-sized allotment in the middle of the South Kensington campus. Within this little retreat from the bustling Exhibition Road were two bee hives, kept and maintained by the society&amp;rsquo;s own committee members. I had a lot of fun in every gardening session I joined, and I even got a chance to attend a &amp;lsquo;hive tour&amp;rsquo; and saw the inside of a hive for the first time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi! My name is Heiloi, but most people just call me Louie. I am currently a PhD Student at Newcastle University looking into active vision in bumblebees.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;//localhost:1313/images/PXL_20241112_120400209.PORTRAIT.jpg&#34; width=&#34;600&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h4&gt;Picture of me at the Francis Crick Institute!&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;my-background&#34;&gt;My Background&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My academic journey began at Imperial College London, where I got a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s in Biology and Master&amp;rsquo;s in Bioinformatics. After that, I was a research assistant at the Francis Crick Institute, where I worked with a neurophysiology lab to investigate multisensory coding in mice brains!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
